<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nashville's Best Real Estate Training - Josh Anderson</title>
    <description>Josh Anderson, a top Real Estate Agent in Nashville, shares his own internal real estate agent training for free. His Real Estate Training, Tips and Advice will help you sell more homes in less time.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 10:23:59 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 10:23:59 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Business Planning Clinic 2020</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/dSJDxxP30qQ?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re invited to attend Business Planning Clinic 2020, where we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the steps you need to take to set yourself up for success in 2020.&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The New Year is just beginning so if you’re having trouble getting your real estate business launched and set up for success in 2020 fear not: You’re officially invited to our Business Planning Clinic on Thursday, Jan 30, at the Green Hills Library. The work you do now will pay dividends in the second and third quarters of this year, and this real estate business planning clinic will guide you on how to set goals and achieve them. If you have any questions at all, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. Promo code 2020BPC. You can RSVP for Business Planning Clinic 2020 by &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eventbrite.com/e/real-estate-business-planning-clinic-tickets-75302005325&quot;&gt;using this link.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; If you have any questions at all, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I look forward to seeing you there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 09:36:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/business-planning-clinic-2020.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/business-planning-clinic-2020.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How I’m Using a Great Book to Teach My Clients About Investing</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/UUdtb4KlUcs?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;I believe that we leave transactions on the table each year by not educating our clients about the benefits of real estate investing. Here&amp;rsquo;s how I&amp;rsquo;m trying to change that.&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just got done reading &lt;em&gt;“The Millionaire Real Estate Investor”&lt;/em&gt; for the third time, and I wanted to let you know about something from it that we’ve been implementing with our clients lately. We’ve been buying copies of the book and are giving it to our past clients, friends, family, and anyone else that might be curious about investing in residential real estate. I think that we’re leaving a handful of transactions a year on the table by not educating our clients about the many benefits of building wealth through investing in real estate. To learn more about this strategy, watch this short video.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 13:33:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-im-using-a-great-book-to-teach-my-clients-about-investing.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-im-using-a-great-book-to-teach-my-clients-about-investing.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Josh Anderson's Journey</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hear how Josh Anderson started his real estate journey, his tips for success, and his vision for the future with The Anderson Group Real Estate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/cTutQkahNF8?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 08:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/josh-andersons-journey.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/josh-andersons-journey.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Entrepreneur Way</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/CfGejDyFsw4?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Originally from Nashville, Josh Anderson graduated from Louisiana State University in International Trade and Finance. Josh served 8 years in the U.S. Army, including a 10-month stint in Bagram, Afghanistan, during Operation Enduring Freedom. These experiences, coupled with the education he received from Louisiana State, have molded him into a focused, disciplined, and strong willed individual. Josh Anderson can best be described as a man of high energy with a passion for Nashville real estate. He is a business savvy professional with a strong desire to cater to his clients’ particular needs. Client satisfaction is paramount! Josh’s market expertise coupled with his superior negotiating skills set him apart from the rest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Find out more here : http://theentrepreneurway.com/contact/ Get daily podcast interviews with successful entrepreneurs by clicking http://theentrepreneurway.com|The Entrepreneur Way&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 15:46:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-entrepreneur-way.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/the-entrepreneur-way.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Josh Anderson on Show #108: Integration as the Secret to Success</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Itob4YH1cbg?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Originally from Nashville, Josh graduated from the Louisiana State University in international trade and finance. Josh served eight years in the U.S Army and can be described as someone with high energy and a strong passion for real estate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In today’s interview, josh talks more about who he is, what he does and why he does it. To learn more, watch our latest video.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 15:40:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/josh-anderson-on-show-108-integration-as-the-secret-to-success.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/josh-anderson-on-show-108-integration-as-the-secret-to-success.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Introducing Our New Real Estate Business Series</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/nE3ngNtcYn4?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To keep you up to date with the best strategies in the real estate business, &lt;strong&gt;we’re going to be sharing with you the things that have worked incredibly well for us over the last few years.&lt;/strong&gt; Keep an eye out in the near future for videos about agent referrals, client events, reviews and review contests, lead generation ideas, and much more—all delivered right to your inbox. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have questions or topics you’re interested in learning about, reach out to us; we’ll get you the answers you need, and we’ll possibly dedicate a whole video to discussing your topic in depth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, feel free to send us any referrals you have! &lt;strong&gt;We’d love to help you or anyone you know with any Nashville real estate needs.&lt;/strong&gt; In the meantime, we look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2019 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/introducing-our-new-real-estate-business-series.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/introducing-our-new-real-estate-business-series.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
